<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  STABLE Update Channel (EveLens 1.x+)
  Old 5.x clients check patch.xml (frozen). New EveLens clients check this file.
-->
<evelens>
  <releases>
    <release>
      <date>2026-04-09</date>
      <version>1.2.1.0</version>
      <url>https://github.com/aliacollins/evelens/releases/tag/v1.2.1</url>
      <autopatchurl>https://github.com/aliacollins/evelens/releases/download/stable/EveLens-install-1.2.1.exe</autopatchurl>
      <autopatchargs>/SILENT</autopatchargs>
      <message><![CDATA[EveLens 1.2.1

BUG FIX:
• Plan training time was significantly underestimated — cerebral accelerator bonuses were being applied permanently to all skills in a plan, regardless of booster expiry. A 225-day plan would show as ~163 days. Training times now use base attributes + implants only, matching the EVE client exactly.

CHANGES:
• Removed unreliable booster auto-detection from training calculations. Booster support will be redesigned with explicit user controls in a future release.
• Added MaxEffectiveAttributePoints cap (32) with regression tests — no attribute can exceed base (27) + implant (5) in calculations.]]></message>
    </release>
    <release>
      <date>2026-04-05</date>
      <version>1.2.0.0</version>
      <url>https://github.com/aliacollins/evelens/releases/tag/v1.2.0</url>
      <autopatchurl>https://github.com/aliacollins/evelens/releases/download/stable/EveLens-install-1.2.0.exe</autopatchurl>
      <autopatchargs>/SILENT</autopatchargs>
      <message><![CDATA[EveLens 1.2.0

NEW FEATURES:
• Drag-to-reorder in Plan Editor — grab skills, multi-select with Shift/Ctrl, prerequisite constraints enforced in real-time
• Chain ribbons & timeline minimap — visual skill grouping by training goal with time distribution
• Skill Farm Dashboard — full economics for extraction characters: Jita pricing, tax, profit projections, Omega sustainability
• Recent Plans menu — quick access to your 5 most recently opened plans
• Skill detail sidebar — double-click any skill to see description, unlocks, enabled items, and plan-to actions
• Keyboard shortcuts — Ctrl+Q, Ctrl+W, Ctrl+N, Ctrl+M, Ctrl+, and more
• Plan import/export overhaul — supports .emp, .txt, and EVE game clipboard format
• Queue health on overview cards — color-coded status dots with at-a-glance queue health

IMPROVEMENTS:
• Gmail-style mail view with inline reading pane
• Employment history toggle between Timeline and List view
• Skill level breakdown tooltip on character header
• macOS install simplified to xattr-only method

BUG FIXES:
• Plan import was creating empty plans — fixed across all import paths (thanks @TinkeringGoblin)
• Skill browser no longer collapses after Plan To (thanks @NotmoGit)
• Windows shutdown no longer hangs — 3-second timeout on save (thanks @Kickunio)
• Market transaction item names no longer blank
• Wallet journal no longer shows "Undefined" for new ESI ref types
• Unicode ship names display correctly
• App no longer hangs on quit with child windows open (macOS)
• New Plan dialog keyboard focus works immediately (thanks @AnszaKalltiern)]]></message>
    </release>
    <release>
      <date>2026-03-29</date>
      <version>1.1.0.0</version>
      <url>https://github.com/aliacollins/evelens/releases/tag/stable</url>
      <autopatchurl>https://github.com/aliacollins/evelens/releases/download/stable/EveLens-install-1.1.0.exe</autopatchurl>
      <autopatchargs>/SILENT</autopatchargs>
      <message><![CDATA[EveLens 1.1.0

Character Skill Comparison, variable font scaling, queue health monitor, ESI token race fix, add character UX, manage groups redesign, blueprint browser, and more.]]></message>
    </release>
  </releases>
</evelens>